<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lisa Wartinger, Author at Plenty International</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/lisa/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/author/lisa/</link>
	<description>Because in all fairness, there is enough...</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 20:18:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Aid provided to Alta Vista School, the Philippines</title>
		<link>/aid-provided-alta-vista-school-philippines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lisa Wartinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 01:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?p=1930</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to everyone who donated to help the village school at Alta Vista, which was hit hard by Typhoon Haiyan.  The superstorm struck the Philippines on November 8, 2013, killing more than 6,000 people and destroying the homes of 15 million more. At the Alta Vista village school all school papers were lost to water [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/aid-provided-alta-vista-school-philippines/">Aid provided to Alta Vista School, the Philippines</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to everyone who donated to help the village school at Alta Vista, which was hit hard by Typhoon Haiyan.  The superstorm struck the Philippines on November 8, 2013, killing more than 6,000 people and destroying the homes of 15 million more.</p>
<p>At the Alta Vista village school all school papers were lost to water damage in the typhoon and the students needed writing tablets and notebooks for lessons. Your donations via Plenty bought school supplies for the 285 children and 48 kids at the day care.  Each student received a notebook and 2 writing tablets, a pen or pencil, an eraser and a pencil sharpener. In total 285 notebooks, 530 notepads, 165 pencils, 120 pens, 165 erasers, 165 sharpeners, plus 50 boxes of crayons and 50 boxes of colored chalk for the daycare were provided. School is over at the end of March, and our friends there told us “this elementary is now set”. Small gestures mean a lot. Thanks for your help.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="/aid-provided-alta-vista-school-philippines/">Aid provided to Alta Vista School, the Philippines</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Typhoon Haiyan &#8211; help needed now!</title>
		<link>/super-typhoon-haiyan-help-needed-now/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lisa Wartinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 07:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?p=1910</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; Super Typhoon Haiyan struck the Philippines with brutal force. Relief efforts are needed on a massive, long-term scale. Plenty is being asked to help the village of Alta Vista on the island of Leyte, which is home to about 1,500 people. Every house in the area lost their roof and/or sustained other damage. Alta [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/super-typhoon-haiyan-help-needed-now/">Super Typhoon Haiyan &#8211; help needed now!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<figure id="attachment_1913" style="width: 300px;" class="wp-caption alignright "><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-1913 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Alta-Vista-School1-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="225" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Alta-Vista-School1-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Alta-Vista-School1-620x465.jpg 620w, /wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Alta-Vista-School1-195x146.jpg 195w, /wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Alta-Vista-School1.jpg 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">The interior of one of the school&#8217;s classrooms after the typhoon.</figcaption></figure>
<p><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-1914 size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/School-ext.-300x225.jpg" alt="School ext." width="300" height="225" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/School-ext.-300x225.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2012/10/School-ext.-620x465.jpg 620w, /wp-content/uploads/2012/10/School-ext.-195x146.jpg 195w, /wp-content/uploads/2012/10/School-ext..jpg 640w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />Super Typhoon Haiyan struck the Philippines with brutal force. Relief efforts are needed on a massive, long-term scale.</p>
<p>Plenty is being asked to help the village of Alta Vista on the island of Leyte, which is home to about 1,500 people. Every house in the area lost their roof and/or sustained other damage. Alta Vista Elementary School, with 280 K-6th grade students, lost its roof, desks, books and supplies. Other schools in the area are in similar shape and need help. DONATIONS ARE NEEDED NOW TO AID THESE COMMUNITY SCHOOLS. We will help as many schools as we can, depending upon the amount of donations we receive. THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO HELP IN A VERY SPECIFIC AND PERSONAL WAY and support the Alta Vista community as they get back on their feet! Choose DONATE in the menu bar and specify &#8220;Typhoon Haiyan&#8221; using the Network for Good option. Thank you!</p>
<p>The post <a href="/super-typhoon-haiyan-help-needed-now/">Super Typhoon Haiyan &#8211; help needed now!</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
