<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Water Archives - Plenty International</title>
	<atom:link href="/area/healthcare/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/area/healthcare/</link>
	<description>Because in all fairness, there is enough...</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:49:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2015 Fall/Winter Plenty Bulletin</title>
		<link>/bulletins/fallwinter-plenty-bulletin-2015/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=2125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fall/Winter Plenty Bulletin 2015</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-plenty-bulletin-2015/">2015 Fall/Winter Plenty Bulletin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/Winter-2015-Plenty-Bulletin.pdf">Fall/Winter Plenty Bulletin 2015</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-plenty-bulletin-2015/">2015 Fall/Winter Plenty Bulletin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2015 Spring/Summer Bulletin</title>
		<link>/bulletins/springsummer-2015/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=2065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>/spring-summer-bulletin-2015/</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/springsummer-2015/">2015 Spring/Summer Bulletin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #000080;"><a style="color: #000080; text-decoration: underline;" title="Spring/Summer 2015 Bulletin" href="/spring-summer-bulletin-2015/">/spring-summer-bulletin-2015/</a></span></strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/springsummer-2015/">2015 Spring/Summer Bulletin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spring-Summer Bulletin 2015</title>
		<link>/spring-summer-bulletin-2015/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 00:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?p=2064</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2015 Spring-Summer Bulletin letter Plenty Bulletin Spring:Summer 2015</p>
<p>The post <a href="/spring-summer-bulletin-2015/">Spring-Summer Bulletin 2015</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><span style="color: #000080;"><strong><a style="color: #000080; text-decoration: underline;" href="/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/2015-Spring-Summer-Bulletin-letter.pdf">2015 Spring-Summer Bulletin letter</a></strong></span></span></p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong><span style="color: #000080;"><a style="color: #000080; text-decoration: underline;" href="/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/Plenty-Bulletin-SpringSummer-2015.pdf">Plenty Bulletin Spring:Summer 2015</a></span></strong></span></p>
<p>The post <a href="/spring-summer-bulletin-2015/">Spring-Summer Bulletin 2015</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2014 Fall/Winter Bulletin</title>
		<link>/bulletins/fallwinter-2014-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2014 20:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=2044</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>November 2014 Dear Friends of Plenty,   You’ve probably heard by now that Plenty’s founder and mentor, Stephen Gaskin passed away on July first of this year, right before our annual Plenty Board meeting. He hadn’t been directly involved with Plenty over the past few years but, without his original inspiration and vision, Plenty would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2014-2/">2014 Fall/Winter Bulletin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">November 2014</p>
<p class="p2">Dear Friends of Plenty,</p>
<p class="p4"><span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>You’ve probably heard by now that Plenty’s founder and mentor, Stephen Gaskin passed away on July first of this year, right before our annual Plenty Board meeting. He hadn’t been directly involved with Plenty over the past few years but, without his original inspiration and vision, Plenty would not have been born. I first met him in 1968 in a church basement in San Francisco where he was holding meetings with a couple of hundred hippies on Thursday nights. Over the course of the following year these meetings grew to about 1,500 and they filled a local rock and roll hall, the Family Dog, on Monday Nights. Stephen would sit on a low wooden platform, talking without a microphone and lead a conversation related to the things we were all thinking about in those days like spirit and energy, war and peace and what could we young hippies do in a country and a world that we believed desperately needed some kind of spiritual awakening. We viewed Monday Night Class as the Continental Congress for the Second American Revolution, a revolution that would be nonviolent and motivated by love, but a real revolution in the sense that we wanted to live very differently based on our discoveries of who we were and what it means to be human. Of course, the late sixties and early seventies were traumatic times with the ever-present specter of an insane war in Vietnam and the assassinations of icons like Martin Luther King, Jr. and Bobby Kennedy. Then came the shooting of four students at Kent State by the National Guard on May 4, 1970.<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>That was on a Monday and that night, when we were gathered in the Family Dog as usual, the voices for arming ourselves and taking it to the streets were especially loud and insistent. It truly felt like the country was on the brink of a generational civil war and Stephen played a pivotal role as a voice for peace, pointing out that, in the first place, we couldn’t win a shooting war and, most importantly, our revolution would be rendered worse than meaningless, just another sorry chapter in the immensely stupid and self-destructive cycle of violence that seemed to have forever plagued our species.</p>
<p class="p4">On October 12 of that year, about 200 of us headed out across America with Stephen who had been invited on a speaking tour at universities and churches and community centers and town halls. We had moved into school buses fitted out with beds and kitchens and wood stoves. The first gig was in Minneapolis. We went to New York City, Philadelphia, Washington, DC, Nashville, Boulder, CO and dozens of cities and towns in between, finally ending up back in San Francisco with the understanding that it was time to put our money where our mouth was.</p>
<p class="p4">The first step was to make a community where we could live together. We decided to head to Tennessee, to get away from the political noise on both coasts and where we might be able to afford land. We got lucky and found a thousand acre farm for $70/acre. In the beginning we were just learning how to farm and feed ourselves and deliver babies and deal with no running water and no electricity. We were very poor but we still felt like we had more than enough to be able to share. Because we had always been committed to effecting change in the world, the next natural step was to start Plenty. Through these early years of the Farm and Plenty, when we were pretty green and wet behind the ears and learning how to get along with each other (by 1974 when we founded Plenty there were about 600 of us) Stephen was an essential guide and I don’t think we could have made it without him. The rest is history and we actually have a book in the works (“The Roots of Plenty”) that will be out before year-end. On top of that, the Farm and Plenty are on display in the Tennessee State Museum in Nashville as part of an Intentional Communities of Tennessee exhibit until the end of November. Imagine that.</p>
<p class="p4">I’d like to sign off with love and a big thank you to Stephen for his courage, vision and perseverance. I want to make a special plea for our friends and colleagues, Bisi and Mahmoud Iderabdullah who manage Imani House International, which has a clinic that’s on the front lines of the Ebola epidemic in Liberia. Two of their staff have died from the disease. They need all the help we can give them. The new Bulletin is full of stories of people who inspire. They’re all on the front lines of the global campaign to make things better, to find and create solutions and to take care of others. They deserve our help.</p>
<p class="p5">With thanks to you from all of us at Plenty,</p>
<p class="p5">Peter Schweitzer</p>
<h5>To view the Fall/Winter 2014 Plenty Bulletin simply click this link:</h5>
<h5><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/Plenty-Bulletin-FallWinter-2014.pdf">Plenty Bulletin Fall/Winter 2014</a></h5>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2014-2/">2014 Fall/Winter Bulletin</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guatemala</title>
		<link>/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/guatemala/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 05:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=1872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Plenty was able to help twelve-year-old Emanuel  to secure an all terrain “Rough Rider” styled wheelchair. Plenty staff ran into Emmanuel in the street at the entrance to the Guatemala City waste dump. A picture of Emanuel sitting in a homemade plastic wheelchair energized the campaign to get him the kind of wheelchair he really [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/guatemala/">Guatemala</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Plenty was able to help twelve-year-old Emanuel  to secure an all terrain “Rough Rider” styled wheelchair. Plenty staff ran into Emmanuel in the street at the entrance to the Guatemala City waste dump. A picture of Emanuel sitting in a homemade plastic wheelchair energized the campaign to get him the kind of wheelchair he really needs with donations provided by board member Robert Reifel and friends in New Mexico, and collaboration with Mark Richards of Hope Haven International. The wheelchair was designed by Whirlwind International and made by the nonprofit Bertha O. de Osete Foundation in Mexico.</p>
<p>Walking through the asentamientos (settlements) next to the Guatemala City dump where Plenty has been supporting a child nutrition project one sees a lot of bare ground with no plant life. Sewage collects in ditches along the pathways between the rows of shanties built from scraps of metal, wood and cardboard. There are no playgrounds or green spaces. Everyone is living on the edge of survival.</p>
<div id="related-pages">
<h3>More in 2013 Fall/Winter Bulletin</h3><ul class='related-list siblings'><li class="page_item page-item-1868"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/kids-country/">KIds To The Country</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1875"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/karens-soy-nutrition-program-guatemala/">Karen&#8217;s Soy Nutrition Program, Guatemala</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1879"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/plenty-belize/">Plenty Belize</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1881"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/books-kids/">Books To Kids</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1885"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/adibe/">ADIBE</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1887"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/essential-seeds-trees-program-chimaltenango-guatemala/">Essential Seeds and Trees Program, Chimaltenango, Guatemala.</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1890"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1894"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/pine-ridge-gardens/">Pine Ridge Gardens</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1897"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/combined-federal-campaign/">Combined Federal Campaign</a></li>
</ul></div><p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/guatemala/">Guatemala</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pine Ridge Gardens</title>
		<link>/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/pine-ridge-gardens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 05:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=1894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This year again over 200 family gardens were supported by the program. Above,  Pine Ridge ranks as one of the poorest reservations in the US, with extremely high rates of heart disease and diabetes. The organic vegetables raised in these gardens directly address these conditions. Many thanks once more to the Philip R. Jonsson Foundation. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/pine-ridge-gardens/">Pine Ridge Gardens</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year again over 200 family gardens were supported by the program. Above,  Pine Ridge ranks as one of the poorest reservations in the US, with extremely high rates of heart disease and diabetes. The organic vegetables raised in these gardens directly address these conditions. Many thanks once more to the Philip R. Jonsson Foundation.</p>
<div id="related-pages">
<h3>More in 2013 Fall/Winter Bulletin</h3><ul class='related-list siblings'><li class="page_item page-item-1868"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/kids-country/">KIds To The Country</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1872"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/guatemala/">Guatemala</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1875"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/karens-soy-nutrition-program-guatemala/">Karen&#8217;s Soy Nutrition Program, Guatemala</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1879"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/plenty-belize/">Plenty Belize</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1881"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/books-kids/">Books To Kids</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1885"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/adibe/">ADIBE</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1887"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/essential-seeds-trees-program-chimaltenango-guatemala/">Essential Seeds and Trees Program, Chimaltenango, Guatemala.</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1890"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1897"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/combined-federal-campaign/">Combined Federal Campaign</a></li>
</ul></div><p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/pine-ridge-gardens/">Pine Ridge Gardens</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Combined Federal Campaign</title>
		<link>/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/combined-federal-campaign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 05:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=1897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Plenty is happy to participate in the 2014 Combined Federal Campaign workplace giving program for federal employees.  Financial contributions federal employees designate to approved nonprofit organizations are matched by the U.S. government.  Contributions that Plenty receives through the CFC are earmarked for its food and agricultural programs in Central America. If you or a family [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/combined-federal-campaign/">Combined Federal Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Plenty is happy to participate in the 2014 Combined Federal Campaign workplace giving program for federal employees.  Financial contributions federal employees designate to approved nonprofit organizations are matched by the U.S. government.  Contributions that Plenty receives through the CFC are earmarked for its food and agricultural programs in Central America. If you or a family member is a federal employee, please choose Plenty as your beneficiary, using CFC # 11625</p>
<div id="related-pages">
<h3>More in 2013 Fall/Winter Bulletin</h3><ul class='related-list siblings'><li class="page_item page-item-1868"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/kids-country/">KIds To The Country</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1872"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/guatemala/">Guatemala</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1875"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/karens-soy-nutrition-program-guatemala/">Karen&#8217;s Soy Nutrition Program, Guatemala</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1879"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/plenty-belize/">Plenty Belize</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1881"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/books-kids/">Books To Kids</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1885"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/adibe/">ADIBE</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1887"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/essential-seeds-trees-program-chimaltenango-guatemala/">Essential Seeds and Trees Program, Chimaltenango, Guatemala.</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1890"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-1894"><a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/pine-ridge-gardens/">Pine Ridge Gardens</a></li>
</ul></div><p>The post <a href="/bulletins/fallwinter-2013/combined-federal-campaign/">Combined Federal Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imani House</title>
		<link>/bulletins/spring-2012/imani-house/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyorg.local/?post_type=bulletins&#038;p=237</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Plenty’s past support helped expand the Imani House Clinic. “The IMANI HOUSE clinic located in Brewerville, Liberia has become an integral part of the Liberian Health care system. It was opened originally to serve thousands of refugees left stranded by the devastating civil war, which began in 1990. IMANI HOUSE works closely with the country’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/imani-house/">Imani House</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Plenty’s past support helped expand the Imani House Clinic. “The IMANI HOUSE clinic located in Brewerville, Liberia has become an integral part of the Liberian Health care system. It was opened originally to serve thousands of refugees left stranded by the devastating civil war, which began in 1990. IMANI HOUSE works closely with the country’s Ministry of Health and local community leaders. The clinic offers full family health care services, with a special pediatrics program, a short-stay in patient facility, family planning and emergency deliveries. In addition the clinic offers dental care, laboratory services, and workshops in first aid, nutrition, basic health care and disease prevention, tutoring, and parent workshops.” </p>
<p><a href="http://www.imanihouse.org/">www.imanihouse.org</a></p>
<div id="related-pages">
<h3>More in Spring 2012</h3><ul class='related-list siblings'><li class="page_item page-item-233"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/guatemala/">Guatemala</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-234"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/karens-soy-nutrition-project/">Karen’s Soy Nutrition Project</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-235"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/el-salvador/">El Salvador</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-236"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/pine-ridge-gardens/">Pine Ridge Gardens</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-41"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/plenty-belize-school-gardens-update/">Plenty Belize: School Gardens Update</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-51"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/gulf-coast-recovery/">Gulf Coast Recovery</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-87"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/soy-projects-update/">Soy Projects Update</a></li>
<li class="page_item page-item-61"><a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/kids-to-the-country-kwanzaa-2011/">Kids to the Country: Kwanzaa 2011</a></li>
</ul></div><p>The post <a href="/bulletins/spring-2012/imani-house/">Imani House</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>25,000 children die each day due to poverty</title>
		<link>/25000-children-die-each-day-due-to-poverty/</link>
					<comments>/25000-children-die-each-day-due-to-poverty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Schweitzer]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 23:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://plentyblog.com/?p=468</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to UNICEF, 25,000 children die every day due to poverty. And they “die quietly in some of the poorest villages on earth, far removed from the scrutiny and the conscience of the world. Being meek and weak in life makes these dying multitudes even more invisible in death.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="/25000-children-die-each-day-due-to-poverty/">25,000 children die each day due to poverty</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to UNICEF, 25,000 children die every day due to poverty. And they “die quietly in some of the poorest villages on earth, far removed from the scrutiny and the conscience of the world. Being meek and weak in life makes these dying multitudes even more invisible in death.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="/25000-children-die-each-day-due-to-poverty/">25,000 children die each day due to poverty</a> appeared first on <a href="/">Plenty International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/25000-children-die-each-day-due-to-poverty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
